Finding Aid for James J. Duderstadt Papers
Bentley Historical Library
- Digital Documents
  - University of Michigan Presidency, 1986-1997; 5397 original digital files (393 MB)
    - Write Files, 1988-1997; 588 original digital files
      - 1994-1995 Write Files, 55 files
        - MSU v. UM, 3/8/1995
        - Political Objectives, 4/20/1995
        - Chart-91, 4/3/1995
        - Charts, 4/3/1995
        - Changes-87-91, 4/3/1995
        - Chart-87, 4/3/1995
        - Football Coaches, 5/13/1995
        - Nona-Test, 6/24/1995
        - Landscaping Ideas, 7/13/1995
        - Regents Memo, 7/16/1995
        - Transformation Text 1.6, 7/24/1995
        - AAU Nominations, 7/28/1995
        - EO FY96 Salaries, 7/30/1995
        - Women 5.0, 7/6/1995
        - Women Ex Sum 5.0, 7/9/1995
        - Pres Budget, 8/10/1995
        - Regents--EO Salaries, 8/16/1995
        - CHS 60, 8/31/1995
        - Kellogg Letter Proposal, 9/11/1994
        - Agenda List, 9/12/1994
        - Newsletter #1, 9/17/1994
      - 1995-1996 Write Files, 75 files
        - Emeritus Guidelines, 1/12/1994
        - Cap Outlay, 1/18/1996
        - Harrison-1/96, 1/18/1996
        - Neal-11/951, 1/20/1995
        - Steffan-1/96, 1/4/1996
        - Max Fisher, 10/1/1995
        - Machen Apt-II, 10/11/1995
        - Damon Keith, 10/12/1995
        - George Slykhouse, 10/12/1995
        - Machen Apt, 10/5/1995
        - Regents-Transition, 10/5/1995
        - Visitors, 10/5/1995
        - Gibson, 10/9/1995
        - Elsa-Salary, 11/16/1995
        - Kinnear-11/95, 11/20/1995
        - Conn-reference, 11/9/1995
        - UCSC-Reference, 11/9/1995
        - Machen-12/95, 12/12/1995
        - Neal-12/95, 12/12/1995
        - JJD Thanks, 12/13/1995
        - Science Ed Notes, 12/24/1989
        - Roberson-2/96, 2/15/1996
        - Summerfield-2/96, 2/19/1996
        - Eng Letter, 2/23/1996
        - Board in Control, 2/26/1996
        - Eng Letter 2, 2/27/1996
        - EO Salaries-96, 2016
        - 1995-1996 Write Files-Miscellaneous, 2016
        - Princeton, 3/15/1996
        - Athletics, 4/3/1996
        - Hillegonds, 4/4/1996
        - History and Traditions, 4/8/1996
        - NAE Letter, 5/10/1996
        - Pritchard, 5/15/1996
        - Sample, 5/16/1996
        - Bio Profile (Short), 5/21/1995
        - Ford, 5/21/1996
        - Campaign-$250 K, 5/7/1996
        - Media Union Program, 5/8/1996
        - President's House, 6/10/1996
        - BICIA, 6/12/1996
        - deans thankyou, 6/13/1996
        - Vennema, 6/18/1996
        - Development, 6/19/1996
        - Delaney, 6/4/1996
        - Levin, 8/16/1996
        - Scientific Integrity, 8/28/1996
        - Science Education 3.0, 8/28/1996
        - Paradigms, 8/28/1996
        - Basic vs. Applied, 8/28/1996
        - Caltech, 8/28/1996
        - Science Education Talk, 8/28/1996
        - Sigma Xi, 8/28/1996
        - Rackham 50th, 8/28/1996
        - Columbia Symposium, 8/28/1996
        - Redrawing Boundaries, 8/28/1996
        - Science H.S. Talk, 8/28/1996
        - Frontier, 8/28/1996
        - Science Manpower, 8/28/1996
        - Research University Notes, 8/28/1996
        - Graduate, 8/28/1996
        - Technology Policy, 8/28/1996
        - Research Videotape, 8/28/1996
        - Nat Econ Council, 8/28/1996
        - Science Policy Book, 8/28/1996
        - Traineeship, 8/28/1996
        - White House-ST/JJD, 8/28/1996
        - NSB-UC-Davis, 8/28/1996
        - Teaching and Research 2.1, 8/28/1996
        - Sidman, 9/20/1995
        - JJD Resign, 9/27/1995
        - Letter to Community, 9/27/1995
        - PAG-1995, 9/27/1995
        - Womack, 9/28/1995
        - Staff Salaries-95, 9/5/1995
      - 1996-1997 Write Files, 8 files
        - JJD Let to Pres, 10/18/1996
        - Dutcher, 2/13/1997
        - Lewis Reference, 2/18/1997
        - Chang-Lin Tien, 2/20/1997
        - WSU Pres Nom, 2/3/1997
        - Hennessey, 3/19/1997
        - Sloan Review, 9/18/1996
        - Higher Ed Statistics, 9/19/1996
    - Legacy, circa 1996; 36 original digital files
      The Legacy Documents subseries (36 original digital files, ca. 1996) contains the drafts of the digital records that resulted in a number of printed publications written by Duderstadt together entitled 'Legacy Documents.' The files in the 'Sunflower' sub-folder are those files that resulted in the publication entitled 'A Growing Season: A Report from the President.. .The University of Michigan, 1986-1996.' A complete set of printed 'Legacy' documents including 'A Growing Season...' is in the Paper Documents series Publications.
      - 1996-1997 Write Files, 8 files
        - UM Seal heavy pict, 2016
        - Athletics Monograph, 7/30/1996
        - Intellect Trans Mono, 8/1/1996
        - Sun/leaders firsts list, 8/1/1996
        - Cost, price, and value, 8/1/1996
        - State of the U, 8/1/1996
        - Sun/agenda,mandate,access, 8/1/1996
        - Education mono, 8/1/1996
        - Strategy appndx 2, 8/1/1996
        - Diversity Intro, 8/1/1996
        - M-Union Mono, 8/1/1996
        - Sun/buildings list, 8/1/1996
        - Sun/agenda list 1, 8/1/1996
        - Diversity&Exc 7.2+hist, 8/1/1996
        - Sun/constant change, 8/1/1996
        - Strategic Plan text, 8/1/1996
        - Sun/leaders top 10 list, 8/1/1996
        - Sun/leaders list, 8/1/1996
        - Strategy appndx 3, 8/1/1996
        - Media U Intro, 8/1/1996
        - Sun/bedrock, 8/1/1996
        - Sun/agenda list 2, 8/1/1996
        - Strategy appendx 1, 8/1/1996
        - Sun/education, 8/1/1996
        - Sun/change, 8/1/1996
        - Strategy appndx 4, 8/1/1996
        - Sun/outreach list, 8/1/1996
        - Sun/leaders text, 8/1/1996
        - Sun/diversity, 8/1/1996
        - Sun/educ list, 8/1/1996
        - Sun/nurture growth, 8/1/1996
        - Sun/rankings list, 8/1/1996
        - Sun/service, 8/1/1996
        - Education intro, 8/1/1996
        - Sun/structure, 8/1/1996
    - Digital Images, circa 1996; 55 original digital files
      The Digital Images subseries (55 original digital files, ca. 1996) provides a look at the many buildings either newly constructed or renovated during Duderstadt's presidential tenure at Michigan. The Ann Arbor campus underwent major changes to the Central, North, Athletic, and Medical campuses. New construction projects include the Media Union, Cancer & Geriatrics Center, Medical Science Research Building, Lurie Engineering Center and Bell Tower, Donald Canham Natatorium, and the Glenn E. Schembechler Hall. Major renovation and improvement projects include Angell Hall, CC Little, Chemistry Building, and Health Service. Included in this series are images of the buildings constructed on the U-M Dearborn and Flint campuses. A complete listing of all construction and renovation projects is highlighted in a special booklet titled 'Rebuilding the University, The University of Michigan 1986-1996.' A copy of this document is in the Paper Documents series Publications.
      - 1996-1997 Write Files, 8 files
        - Digital Images, 2016
  - Faculty Archives, 1968-ongoing; 1312 digital files
    Includes speeches, presentations, writings and images. Portions of the collection are restricted. This collection represents the 'personal papers' of president Duderstadt.
    - The Domestic Control of the United States Atomic Energy Program, 1965
    - Lecture Notes from Feynman Quantum Mechanics Course, Caltech, 1967
    - Lecture Notes from Feynman Elementary Particles Course, Caltech, 1968
    - The Theory of Neutron Wave Propagation, 1968
    - Nuclear Reactor Analysis Working Text, Volume One, 1973
    - Nuclear Reactor Analysis Working Text, Volume Two, 1973
    - A Comparison of Projection operator formalisms for the study of self-diffusion, 4/18/1973
    - Nuclear Reactor Kinetics Course Notes, 1975
    - Nuclear Reactor Analysis, 1976
    - Nuclear Power: Technology on Trial Draft, 1978
    - Inertial Confinement Fusion Draft, 1979
    - The College of Engineering Status and Future Planning Document Update, 1981
    - The College of Engineering: Status and Future A Presentation for the Executive Officers, 1981
    - College of Engineering: One-Year and Five-Year Budget Planning Document, 1982
    - Engineering Education at Michigan: Crisis Challenge and Opportunity, 1982
    - Engineering Education at Michigan: Crisis Challenge and Opportunity, 1983
    - From the Dean of the College of Engineering at University of Michigan, 1983
    - High Technology in Michigan: Silicon Valley or Appalachia, 1983
    - Nuclear Reactor Theory and Analysis I, A Workbook Supporting Video Course, The Departtment of Nuclear Engineering Videotape Curriculum, 1983
    - Nuclear Reactor Theory and Analysis II, A Workbook Supporting Video Course, The Departtment of Nuclear Engineering Videotape Curriculum, 1983
    - A Special Report on Development From the College of Engineering at University of Michigan, 1983
    - College of Engineering Briefing, 1984
    - Intellectual Inventory, 1984
    - North Campus Planning Study: The University of Michigan, 1984
    - A Proposal to Support the Computer-Aided Engineering Network, 1984
    - Reactor Fluid Mechanics, A Workbook Supporting Video Course, The Department of Nuclear Engineering Videotape Curriculum, 1984
    - Thermal Analysis of Nucelar Reactors, A Workbook Supporting Video Course, The Department of Nuclear Engineering Videotape Curriculum, 1984
    - A Unique Opportunity for Michigan's Future: An Investment in Engineering Excellence Rationale and Plan, 1984
    - The Crisis Facing Engineering Education in Michigan: A Call for Action, 1985
    - Executive Committee Retreat Supporting Materials, 1985
    - A Proposal to Establish a Center of Scholarly Excellence in Advanced Electronics and Optics Technology, 1985
    - A Proposal to Establish a Center of Scholarly Excellence in Complex Manufacturing Technology, 1985
    - A Proposal to Establish a Center of Scholarly Excellence in Machine Intelligence Technology, 1985
    - State of the UM: College of Engineering, 1985
    - A Unique Opportunity for Michigan's Future: An Investment in Engineering Excellence, 1985
    - University of Michgan FY85-86 State Budget Request: College of Engineering, 1985
    - Alumni Address 1986
    - Briefing to Chinese Educators 1986
    - Budget Priorities Committee 1986
    - Engineering NAC Meeting 1986
    - Express Site Visit 1986
    - Medical School Faculty Presentation 1986
    - A Mission for the 21st Century: Building Leadership for Tomorrow on a Foundation of Academic Excellence, 1986
    - National Honor Society 1986
    - New Faculty Welcome 1986
    - Presentation to Housing Staff 1986
    - Provost Address to Senate Assembly 1986
    - Rose Bowl Welcome 1986
    - State Legislature Briefings 1986
    - Student Welcome 1986
    - 1987 Graduate Education
    - Academic Affairs Diversity, 1987
    - Alumni Reunion, 1987
    - Alumni Scholars, 1987
    - Caltech Address, 1987
    - Commitment to Pluralism, 1987
    - Deans-EO Kickoff Picnic, 1987
    - Development, 1987
    - Educating for Change, 1987
    - Ethics and Value Conference, 1987
    - Faculty Senate Assembly, 1987
    - Football Training Table, 1987
    - Freshman Convocation, 1987
    - Graduate Student Welcome, 1987
    - Grand Rapids Economics Club, 1987
    - High Technology, 1987
    - Homecoming Welcome, 1987
    - Human Genetics, 1987
    - ICPSR Welcome, 1987
    - Industrial Technology Institute Dedication, 1987
    - Inglis House Faculty Dinners, 1987
    - Legislators Briefing, 1987
    - Michigan Football Bust, 1987
    - Michigan Information Technology Network, 1987
    - Minority Education, 1987
    - Minority Student Welcome, 1987
    - NIH Centennial Luncheon, 1987
    - National Nursing Association, 1987
    - New Faculty Welcome, 1987
    - Niara Sudarkasa Farewell, 1987
    - Parents Orientation, 1987
    - Physics Address, 1987
    - Physics Lecture, 1987
    - Physics-Department, 1987
    - Shapiro Farewell Dinner, 1987
    - Solid State Lab Dedication, 1987
    - Space Physics Research Lab, 1987
    - State Budget Request Narrative, 1987
    - Student-Athlete Reception, 1987
    - US-Japan Conference, 1987
    - Yale Talk, 1987
    - 1988 Introduction to MLK Event
    - Academic Affairs Agenda 1988
    - Alumni-Rose Bowl, 1988
    - Alumni-Short, 1988
    - Athletes Reception, 1988
    - Big Ten Development Officers, 1988
    - Blanchard Tuition Discussions, 1988
    - Booth Newspapers, 1988
    - Canham Dedication, 1988
    - The Challenge of Change: Inaugural Address, 1988
    - Commencement-Fall-1988f
    - Computer-Medicine, 1988
    - Congressional Delegation 1, 1988
    - Congressional Delegation 2, 1988
    - Costs of Higher Education, 1988
    - Deans Term End Dinner, 1988
    - Deans-EO Kickoff, 1988
    - Diversity Notes, 1988
    - Engineering Commencement-88, 1988
    - Eye on the Ball, 1988
    - FY88-89 Budget, 1988
    - Faculty Awards, 1988
    - Football Bust- Add ins, 1988
    - Football Bust-88, 1988
    - Freshman Convocation, 1988
    - Futures Talk, 1988
    - General Talk, 1988
    - General Talk-Rose Bowl, 1988
    - Grad Welcome, 1988
    - HBCU Remarks, 1988
    - Honors Convocation, 1988
    - IFS Reception, 1988
    - Inaugural Breakfast, 1988
    - Inaugural Luncheon, 1988
    - Inaugural Student Picnic, 1988
    - Inauguration 1.2, 1988
    - Inauguration Final Speech, 1988
    - Inauguration Remarks List, 1988
    - Inauguration Week Talks, 1988
    - Investments, 1988
    - Lead Network 1.2, 1988
    - Lead Network 1.4, 1988
    - Lead Network Talk 1.3, 1988
    - Legislative Luncheon, 1988
    - Legislature, 1988
    - Medical Center Reception, 1988
    - Medical Education, 1988
    - Michigan Challenge, 1988
    - Michigan Mandate 1.4, 1988
    - Michigan Mandate 2, 1988
    - Michigan Mandate 2.2, 1988
    - Michigan Mandate 2.2C, 1988
    - Michigan Mandate 2C, 1988
    - The Michigan Mandate: A Strategic Linking of Excellence and Diversity, 1988
    - Mission Planning, 1988
    - Mission Statement, 1988
    - NASA ERCs, 1988
    - NSF-MSF Conference, 1988
    - New Detroit, 1988
    - New Faculty Welcome 2.1, 1988
    - New Faculty Welcome 2.1S, 1988
    - Opening Remarks, 1988
    - Parents Orientation 2.0, 1988
    - Presidential Fall Weekend, 1988
    - Rackham 50th, 1988
    - Rackham 50th 1.4, 1988
    - Radiogenic Dedication, 1988
    - Rain Commencement, 1988
    - Resident Talk, 1988
    - SSC Testimony, 1988
    - Scripps-Howard, 1988
    - Speech Topics, 1988
    - State Appropriations Test, 1988
    - State of the University, 1988
    - State of the University Address, 1988
    - Student Inaugural Address, 1988
    - Student Inaugural Address 1.1, 1988
    - Student Inaugural Address 1.5, 1988
    - Traxler-Bloch, 1988
    - UM Flint Dedication, 1988
    - UMF Commencement, 1988
    - Undergraduate Education, 1988
    - Volunteer Leadership, 1988
    - Yale Alumni Talk, 1988
    - Yale Science & Engineering, 1988
    - AAU Welcome, 1989
    - Aerospace Dedication, 1989
    - Alumni (Major Gifts), 1989
    - Alumni (Volunteers) 2.0, 1989
    - Alumni 5.0, 1989
    - Alumni Talks, 1989
    - Alumni-March-89, 1989
    - Basketball Bust -- March 28, 1989
    - Bo Press Release, 1989
    - CBS Interview Questions, 1989
    - Caltech Commencement Address, 1989
    - Campaign 89, 1989
    - Campaign Ideas, 1989
    - Campaign Wrap-up, 1989
    - Case Statement - June, 1989
    - Case Statement - March, 1989
    - Chemistry Dedication, 1989
    - Chemistry Lunch, 1989
    - Citizens Research Council, 1989
    - Coaches Reception, 1989
    - Coaches Talk, 1989
    - Commence-Fall-89, 1989
    - Commencement-1989
    - Community Outreach, 1989
    - Congressional Breakfast, 1989
    - Continuity and Chaos, 1989
    - Corporate Remarks, 1989
    - Costs of Education, 1989
    - Detroit Economics Club 1.1, 1989
    - EDUCOM Panel, 1989
    - EDUCOM Panel Intro, 1989
    - EDUCOM Press, 1989
    - EDUCOM Welcome, 1989
    - EO-SACUA-Student Retreat, 1989
    - Education, 1989
    - Education 1.0, 1989
    - Education 1.3, 1989
    - Education Notes, 1989
    - Emerging Economies, 1989
    - External Interactions, 1989
    - Football Building Kickoff 2, 1989
    - Football Bust 2.0, 1989
    - Freshman Convocation 3.0, 1989
    - Graduate Welcome 3.0, 1989
    - Grand Rapids Economics Club, 1989
    - Higher Education 1.0, 1989
    - Hispanic Heritage, 1989
    - Homecoming-89, 1989
    - Honors Convocation-1989
    - House Appropriations Committee, 1989
    - IPPS Talk, 1989
    - Intern Forum (9-89), 1989
    - International Issues, 1989
    - Internationalization, 1989
    - JJD Student Letter, 1989
    - LA Major Gifts, 1989
    - Lagatus, 1989
    - Leadership Network 2.0, 1989
    - Leadership Retreat, 1989
    - Listen and Learn, 1989
    - Los Angeles Dinner, 1989
    - M-Club Talk, 1989
    - MLK Opening, 1989
    - MLK-Business and Finance, 1989
    - MLK-Unity March, 1989
    - Major Gifts Address 2.0, 1989
    - Major Gifts Meeting, 1989
    - Michigan Add-Ins 1.0, 1989
    - Michigan Economy 1. 11-6-89.pdf, 1989
    - Michigan Higher Ed 1.0, 1989
    - Michigan Higher Ed 2.2, 1989
    - Michigan Mandate, 1989
    - Michigan Talks 2.0, 1989
    - Michigan UM 1., 1989
    - Minority Welcome 3.0, 1989
    - Mortar Board, 1989
    - NAACP Talk, 1989
    - NAE Meeting, 1989
    - NY Business Lunch, 1989
    - New Faculty Welcome 3.0d, 1989
    - New Faculty Welcome 3.1, 1989
    - Newsweek notes, 1989
    - Parents Orientation 3.0, 1989
    - Parents Weekend, 1989
    - Parents Weekend 2.0, 1989
    - Paw Wow-89, 1989
    - Phi Beta Kappa, 1989
    - Press Conference, 1989
    - Rain Commencement, 1989
    - Regents Retreat, 1989
    - Response to Governor Attack, 1989
    - The Role of the Research University in Undergraduate Education, 1989
    - Rose Bowl (89-90), 1989
    - Rose Bowl Band Rehearsal, 1989
    - Rose Bowl Follow-up, 1989
    - Rose Bowl Welcome Home, 1989
    - Rose Bowl-1989
    - Rotary, 1989
    - Science Education, 1989
    - Semiconductor Conference, 1989
    - Senate Republican Caucus, 1989
    - State Plan, 1989
    - State Strategy 2, 1989
    - State Strategy-89, 1989
    - State Support, 1989
    - State of University Speech, 1989
    - State of the University Address, 1989
    - State of the University Text, 1989
    - Student Recognition Award, 1989
    - Studies in Religion, 1989
    - Taubman Conference, 1989
    - Tentative Speech Topics, 1989
    - Tuition Retreat, 1989
    - UGLI Dedication, 1989
    - Women's Issue, 1989
    - Women's Issues: An Agenda For Action, 1989
    - The Age of Knowledge, 1990
    - Alumni Talk 6.0, 1990
    - Appropriations Committee, 1990
    - Asian American, 1990
    - Athletes Reception, 1990
    - Automotive Conference 4-2-90, 1990
    - Basketball Bust-90, 1990
    - Battle Creek HS, 1990
    - Big Ten 12-2-90, 1990
    - Big Ten-UM$, 1990
    - Bo's Farewells, 1990
    - Business Plan-1990s
    - Campaign, 1990
    - Campaign Briefing-1990
    - Campaign Go/No Go, 1990
    - Campaign Pitch-Alumni, 1990
    - Campaign-Color, 1990
    - Campaign-Color-update, 1990
    - Campaign-Plan, 1990
    - Chamber of Commerce, 1990
    - Commence-Fall-90, 1990
    - Commencement-Spring-90, 1990
    - Communication, 1990
    - Congressional Breakfast, 1990
    - Costs Prices Values 3.0, 1990
    - Demographics, 1990
    - Development, 1990
    - Duderstadt e-mail, 1990
    - Economics Dinner Group, 1990
    - The Economics of Higher Education, 1990
    - Engineering Comm., 1990
    - Engler Add-in, 1990
    - Ethnic Studies Luncheon (10-90), 1990
    - Eye on the Ball-II, 1990
    - Faculty Welcome 4.2, 1990
    - Flint Rotary, 1990
    - Fresh Convocation 4.3, 1990
    - Freshman Convocation 4.3, 1990
    - GM Spirit Awards, 1990
    - Graduate Welcome 4.1, 1990
    - Hartford Sermon 2.0 (act), 1990
    - Hartford Sermon 2.1, 1990
    - High School Science Visit, 1990
    - ITI Meeting, 1990
    - JJD Student Letter, 1990
    - K-12 Education Cranbrook, 1990
    - Leadership Retreat, 1990
    - Leadership Retreat-F90, 1990
    - Library Science (10-90), 1990
    - MLK Closing, 1990
    - MLK Welcome, 1990
    - Major Gifts Committee 1.0, 1990
    - Manufacturing Forum, 1990
    - Maternal and Child Health, 1990
    - Medical School Discussion, 1990
    - Michigan Crossroads 1.0 (June), 1990
    - Michigan Crossroads 1.0 (October), 1990
    - Michigan Economy 1.0, 1990
    - Michigan Mandate 10, 1990
    - Michigan Mandate 3.0, 1990
    - The Michigan Mandate A Strategic Linking of Academic Excellence and Social Diversity, 1990
    - Michigan Mandate III, 1990
    - The Michigan Mandate: Bridge to Opportunity - Opening of the UM Detroit Admission Office, 1990
    - Michigan Outreach Talk 1.0, 1990
    - Michigan Outreach Talk 1.1, 1990
    - Michigan at the Crossroads: The Future of Public Higher Education in Michigan, 1990
    - Midland Talk, 1990
    - Minority Welcome 4.1, 1990
    - NASULGC-Activism, 1990
    - NASULGC-Plan, 1990
    - NSB Presentation, 1990
    - NSF T&R 1.0, 1990
    - National Science Board, 1990
    - New Faculty Welcome 3.1, 1990
    - New Faculty Welcome 3.2, 1990
    - No Code, 1990
    - Notes for Speeches (August, 1990)
    - Notes for Speeches (March, 1990)
    - Overarching Themes, 1990
    - PAC-June-90, 1990
    - Parents Orientation 4.1, 1990
    - Parents Weekend, 1990
    - Parents Weekend 3.0, 1990
    - Physics Notes, 1990
    - Pres. Council Forum, 1990
    - Pres. Council Forum 1, 1990
    - Presidents Club, 1990
    - Presidents Club Finale, 1990
    - Presidents Council Forum-Detroit, 1990
    - Presidents Council Forums Speech, 1990
    - Public Education 4.0, 1990
    - Public Education 4.2, 1990
    - Public Education in America: Crisis in an Age of Knowledge, 1990
    - Rackham, 1990
    - Regents-December, 1990
    - Santa Fe Institute 1.0, 1990
    - Science Awards, 1990
    - Science Education, 1990
    - Science Education 1.4, 1990
    - Science Education 2.0, 1990
    - Senate Assembly 1.3, 1990
    - Service Awards, 1990
    - Solar Car, 1990
    - State of the University, 1990
    - State of the University Address, 1990
    - Student Leadership, 1990
    - Summary 1989-90, 1990
    - Tanner Lecture, 1990
    - Teaching v Research Notes, 1990
    - Title List, 1990
    - To Do-1991, 1990
    - Traverse City Talk, 1990
    - UG Notes, 1990
    - UM Dearborn, 1990
    - UM Dearborn Dedication, 1990
    - UM Inputs and Outputs, 1990
    - UM Organization, 1990
    - Undergraduate, 1990
    - United Way, 1990
    - The University of Michigan, 1990
    - Wallenberg Lecture, 1990
    - AAU Notes, 1991
    - AAU PC, 1991
    - Academic Freedom 1.2, 1991
    - Academic Values 2.2, 1991
    - Academic Values 2.3, 1991
    - Academic Women's Caucus, 1991
    - An Address to The Economic Club: College Presidents Attempt to Reform Intercollegiate Athletics, 1991
    - All Graduate Rankings, 1991
    - Angell Society Detroit, 1991
    - Appropriations Hear PCSUM, 1991
    - Appropriations Hearings 4.0, 1991
    - Appropriations House Republicans, 1991
    - Appropriations Testimony, 1991
    - Athenaeum Project, 1991
    - Attack on Values 1.2, 1991
    - BHEF Odds and Ends, 1991
    - Big Ten List, 1991
    - Brainstorming Ideas, 1991
    - Business Higher Education Forum, 1991
    - Campaign Finale, 1991
    - Campaign Kickoff, 1991
    - Campaign Pitches, 1991
    - Campaign-Individual, 1991
    - College Sports 1.2, 1991
    - Commence-Cards-JJD, 1991
    - Commence-JJD Cards, 1991
    - Commencement Notes, 1991
    - Commencement Thank you, 1991
    - Commencement-JJD Version, 1991
    - Commencement-JJD2, 1991
    - Congressional Breakfast, 1991
    - Cover letter Rankings, 1991
    - Cover letter Rankings 1.0, 1991
    - Development Advisory Group, 1991
    - Doctoral Pipeline Issue, 1991